

#### CONTACT WITH ME

Thống Nhất, Phường 11, Gò Vấp, Hồ Chí Minh

nglethien.minh@gmail.com

0792208228

#### SKILL SUMMARY

- ReactJS
- HTML/CSS/JS
- Nodejs
- Java Springboot
- MongoDB
- Microsoft SQL

# PERSONAL SKILL

- · Good teamworking skills
- · Quick learner to new concepts
- · Hard working

# HOBBIES

- Reading book
- Photography
- · Wake up early and listening podcast

#### CERTIFICATE

- Global Discovery Programme: Intensive English Proficiency Course while studying English in Brunei.
- Certificate of Attendance when participating in Study Tour in Japan.

# NGUYEN LE THIEN MINH

# FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

#### ABOUT ME

While I have been working as a Frontend Developer for the past 2 years, I am eager to transition my skills to the backend side of development with the aim of attaining the position of Senior FullStack Developer within the next 4 years. Through dedicated learning and professional development, I aspire to achieve excellence in my field. My professional experiences include:

- HTML5, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, ReactJS, Angular, bootstrap, Material UI, Responsive web
- RESTful APIs with Java Spring Boot, NodeJs with express
- Axios, react-i18n, ag-grid, apexcharts, devextreme,...
- Jira, SourceTree, git
- MicrosoftSQL, MongoDB

## EXPERIENCE

Company: SENSE ERP (04/2021 - 01/2023)

The Sense ERP Co., Ltd specializes in consulting, building, and providing enterprise management software solutions.

Position: Front-end Developer ReactJs

1. Viethomnay (Recruitment website)

Team size: 4
Responsibilities

- Working in SCRUM team
- Write query to call GraphQL APIs.
- Create new features/react UI component.
- Scraping data for market research and data analysis purposes.

# **Technologies**

- Manage tools: git + SourceTree, Jira
- ReactJs, React hook form + yup, MUI (Material-UI)
- GraphQL, MongoDB, microservice, NodeJs

#### 2. Sense ERP Management

Team size: 7
Responsibilities

- Working in SCRUM team
- Developing new user-facing features using React.js and integrating with API services.
- Researching and integrating components from third-party libraries into the project.
- Collaborating with UX/UI designers to ensure the best user experience and design implementation.
- Writing reusable, efficient, and scalable code following best practices and coding standards.

#### **Technologies**

- Manage tools: git + SourceTree, Jira
- ReactJs, MUI (Material-UI), DevExtreme, ag-grid, apexcharts, Redux, google map APIs
- Microsoft SQL

# Company: FPT Software (09/2020 - 12/2020)

FPT Software is a multinational software company headquartered in Hanoi, Vietnam. The company was established in 1999 and is currently one of the largest software companies in Vietnam.

**Position: Intern** 

1. PROJECT - WEB SECURITY

Team size: 200 Responsibilities

- Test manual modules, functions
- Create mockup pages

# **Technologies**

- Tools: git + SourceTree, Jira
- HTML5, CSS, JavaScript
- Java Spring, Microsoft SQL

# PERSONAL PROJECT

1. Library Management System

Team size: 4
Responsibilities

- Building APIs using Java Spring Boot, design database
- Processing logic and interacting with servers
- · Securing the system

# Technologies

- Tools: git + SourceTree
- Thymeleaf, HTML5, CSS
- Java Spring Boot, Microsoft SQL, JPA

#### Source code

Back-end: https://github.com/Thienminh1999/Library\_Project\_API

2. Ecommerce Web Application

Team size: 1 Responsibilities

- Building APIs using Express, Nodejs
- Design database with MongoDB
- Developing UI features using ReactJs framework and integrating with API services
- Securing the system with session, cookie

# **Technologies**

- Nodejs, Express, MongoDB
- ReactJs

#### Source code

Back-end: https://github.com/Thienminh1999/ecommerce-asm3
Front-end client: https://github.com/Thienminh1999/ecommerce-client
Front-end admin: https://github.com/Thienminh1999/ecommerce-admin

#### **EDUCATION**

# **FPT University**

Software Engineer | 10/2018 - 05/2022

- Learned about the entire software development process, including requirements gathering, system design, coding and development, testing and debugging, deployment and implementation, and maintenance and support.
- While studying, gained experience in coding the back-end for a library management system with QR code integration using Java Spring Boot.
- My graduation project is recruitment website similar to topcv, itviet, etc., using MongoDB and GraphQL.